import '../classes/quiz_class.dart';

List<QuizQuestion> bleachQuestions = [
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Which of the following Captain's Bankai is a Rocket Launcher?",
      answer1: "Sui-Feng",
      answer2: "KANAME TOSEN",
      answer3: "Yoruichi Shihoin",
      answer4: "RETSU UNOHANA",
      correctAnswer: "Sui-Feng"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is the name of Kisuke Urahara's zanpakuto?",
      answer1: "SHINSO",
      answer2: "KANAME TOSEN",
      answer3: "Benihime",
      answer4: "SODE NO SHIRAYUK",
      correctAnswer: "Benihime"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Hado No. 4 is...?",
      answer1: "SHINSO",
      answer2: "Dragon",
      answer3: "The perfect prison",
      answer4: "Byakurai",
      correctAnswer: "Byakurai"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Minazuki is the name of whose zanpakuto?",
      answer1: "Retsu unohana",
      answer2: "Yoruichi Shihoin",
      answer3: "The perfect prison",
      answer4: "RETSU UNOHANA",
      correctAnswer: "Retsu unohana"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Zaraki Kenpachi is the third person to hold the title of 'Kenpachi'?",
      answer1: "Yes",
      answer2: "No",
      answer3: "Never",
      answer4: "the first one",
      correctAnswer: "No"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is the middle name of Yamamoto Genryusai?",
      answer1: "Shigekuni",
      answer2: "Bleach",
      answer3: "TOSEN",
      answer4: "Feng",
      correctAnswer: "Shigekuni"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Orihime's Six hairpins turn into a group of Six pixies known as?",
      answer1: "Shun shun Rikai",
      answer2: "Shin Rikai",
      answer3: "Shun Shun Rakai",
      answer4: "None of the above",
      correctAnswer: "Shun shun rika"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is the inital command and name of Marechiyo Omaeda's zanpakuto?",
      answer1: "Crush gegetsuburi",
      answer2: "The bomb sword",
      answer3: "Axe",
      answer4: "None of the above",
      correctAnswer: "Crush gegetsuburi"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
      question: "In the Menos Catagory which is the top class of Menos?",
      answer1: "Espada",
      answer2: "Hallow",
      answer3: "Shinigami",
      answer4: "Vasto Lordus",
      correctAnswer: "Vasto Lordus"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is the name of the Hollow which attacked the Kurosaki clinic in the very 1st episode?",
      answer1: "Fishbone e",
      answer2: "Fishbone d",
      answer3: "Fishbone f",
      answer4: "Fishbone a",
      correctAnswer: "Fishbone d"
  ),


  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is the human name of Acidwire?",
      answer1: "Sora inoue",
      answer2: "Espada",
      answer3: "He does not have a name",
      answer4: "Yamto",
      correctAnswer: "Sora inoue"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
      question: "The name of Ichigo's mother was?",
      answer1: "Masaki",
      answer2: "Marth",
      answer3: "Carle",
      answer4: "none of the above",
      correctAnswer: "Masaki"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Coyote Starrk is the Primera Espada and thus is the strongest?",
      answer1: "Yes",
      answer2: "No",
      answer3: "Never",
      answer4: "Sometimes",
      correctAnswer: "No"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is the name of Shunsui Kyoraku's zanpakuto?",
      answer1: "The sun",
      answer2: "Crush gegetsuburi",
      answer3: "Rocket Launcher",
      answer4: "Katen kyototsu",
      correctAnswer: "Katen kyototsu"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
      question: "The name of Rukia's zanpakuto is Sode no Shiroyuki?",
      answer1: "Yes",
      answer2: "No",
      answer3: "Katen kyototsu",
      answer4: "Ice age",
      correctAnswer: "No"
  ),


  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Gin Ichimaru's favourite fooditem is?",
      answer1: "Dried persimmons",
      answer2: "Ramen",
      answer3: "Soba",
      answer4: "Sea food",
      correctAnswer: "Dried persimmons"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Bykuya Kuchiki has been the Captain of the 6th Division for roughly 50 years?",
      answer1: "Yes",
      answer2: "No",
      answer3: "Never",
      answer4: "Sometimes",
      correctAnswer: "Yes"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
      question: "The name of Ichigo Kurosaki's Bankai?",
      answer1: "Tensa zangetsu",
      answer2: "Crush gegetsuburi",
      answer3: "none of this",
      answer4: "Katen kyototsu",
      correctAnswer: "Tensa zangetsu"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is the name of the prison cell in which Aizen is being kept after his defeat at the hands of Ichigo?",
      answer1: "Hell prison",
      answer2: "Soul socicty Prison",
      answer3: "Mugen",
      answer4: "Zanpakuto prison",
      correctAnswer: "Mugen"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Who is the author of bleach's manga?",
      answer1: "Tite kudo",
      answer2: "Oda",
      answer3: "Isuami",
      answer4: "Akira",
      correctAnswer: "Tite kudo"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Who is the author of the manga?",
      answer1: "Tite kudo",
      answer2: "Oda",
      answer3: "Isuami",
      answer4: "Akira",
      correctAnswer: "Tite kudo"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Who gave Yachiru Kusajishi her name?",
      answer1: "Yoruichi Shihoin",
      answer2: "Sui-Feng",
      answer3: "Kenpachi Zaraki",
      answer4: "KANAME TOSEN",
      correctAnswer: "Kenpachi Zaraki"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is the identity of Jushiro Ukitake?",
      answer1: "Captain of the Squad 13",
      answer2: "Captain of the Squad 10",
      answer3: "Captain of the Squad 2",
      answer4: "Captain of the Squad 9",
      correctAnswer: "Captain of the Squad 13"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
      question: "When Ichigo Kurosaki save Rukia from execution, which item did he use?",
      answer1: "Tentoken",
      answer2: "His sword",
      answer3: "Renji weapon",
      answer4: "none of the above",
      correctAnswer: "Tentoken"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Where was Rukia executed?",
      answer1: "Hueco Mundo",
      answer2: "Soul king Palace",
      answer3: "Rukongai",
      answer4: "Sokyoku Hill",
      correctAnswer: "Sokyoku Hill"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "who is the fourth espada?",
      answer2: "Ulquiorra Cifer",
      answer3: "Aaroniero Arruruerie",
      answer4: "Nelliel Tu Odelschwanck",
      answer1: "Kugo Ginjo",
      correctAnswer: "Ulquiorra Cifer"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What's the full name of the captain commander?",
      answer2: "Yamamoto Genryuusai Shigekuni",
      answer3: "Sōsuke Aizen",
      answer4: "Renji Abarai",
      answer1: "Kugo Ginjo",
      correctAnswer: "Yamamoto Genryuusai Shigekuni"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is the name of the final Getsuga Tenshou?",
      answer2: "Final Getsuga Tenshou",
      answer3: "Sun Light",
      answer4: "Moon Light",
      answer1: "Mugetsu",
      correctAnswer: "Mugetsu"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is the benki of Shigekuni Yamamoto?",
      answer2: "Tensa Zangetsu",
      answer3: "Senbonzakura Kageyoshi",
      answer4: "Zanka no Tachi",
      answer1: "Minazuki",
      correctAnswer: "Zanka no Tachi"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is the number of the espade grimmjow?",
      answer2: "Four",
      answer3: "Five",
      answer4: "Six",
      answer1: "Seven",
      correctAnswer: "Six"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Which of these is the lowest level of a Menos?",
      answer2: "Gin",
      answer3: "Espade",
      answer4: "Hollow",
      answer1: "None Of The Above",
      correctAnswer: "Gillian"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is the source of ichigo's hollow?",
      answer2: "His Mother",
      answer3: "His Father",
      answer4: "An Experiment",
      answer1: "His Friend",
      correctAnswer: "His Mother"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Who is the leader that Betrayed Aizen?",
      answer2: "Gin",
      answer3: "Renji ",
      answer4: "Byakuya",
      answer1: "None Of The Above",
      correctAnswer: "Gin"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Who was the first shinigami Ichigo met?",
      answer2: "His Father",
      answer3: "His Mother",
      answer4: "His Friend",
      answer1: "His Neighbor",
      correctAnswer: "His Father"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is the name of the 11th squad captain?",
      answer2: "Kenpachi",
      answer3: "Ikkaku",
      answer4: "Shinji",
      answer1: "Jūshirō",
      correctAnswer: "Kenpachi"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is ichigo's father name?",
      answer2: "Isshin",
      answer3: "Jūshirō",
      answer4: "Shinji",
      answer1: "Ikkaku ",
      correctAnswer: "Isshin"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "How many guard squads exist in Soul Society?",
      answer2: "Eleven",
      answer3: "Twelve",
      answer4: "Thirteen",
      answer1: "Fourteen",
      correctAnswer: "Thirteen"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "How did Kenpachi Zaraki become a captain?",
      answer2: "By killing the previous captain",
      answer3: "By Ranking Up",
      answer4: "By Doing Missions",
      answer1: "All Of The Above",
      correctAnswer: "By killing the previous captain"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Who is the leader of the Shinigami Women's Association?",
      answer2: "Yachiru Kusajishi",
      answer3: "Rukia Kuchiki",
      answer4: "Orihime Inoue",
      answer1: "Nel tu",
      correctAnswer: "Yachiru Kusajishi"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "How did Rukia explain the Shinigami world to Ichigo?",
      answer2: "By Speaking Him",
      answer3: "Showing him a documentary  movie",
      answer4: "Drawing Cute Little Pictures",
      answer1: "None of the Above",
      correctAnswer: "Drawing Cute Little Pictures"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "what is the release date of bleach the last part?",
      answer1: "2019",
      answer2: "2020",
      answer3: "2021",
      answer4: "2022",
      correctAnswer: "2021"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is the episode that ichigo's hollow appear?",
      answer1: "Ninteen",
      answer2: "Twenty Four",
      answer3: "Thirty Five",
      answer4: "Fourty Six",
      correctAnswer: "Ninteen"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is the only way to skip from hell?",
      answer1: "By Becoming Hollows",
      answer2: "Ichigo's hollow",
      answer3: "By Becoming Humans",
      answer4: "None of The Above",
      correctAnswer: "Ichigo's hollow"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is the animal that yoruichi shihouin love?",
      answer1: "Cat",
      answer2: "Dog",
      answer3: "Lion",
      answer4: "Wolf",
      correctAnswer: "Cat"
  ),

];